<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fabio Fontana</title>
    <link>https://fabifont.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Fabio Fontana</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fabifont.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Download packages with systemd-timer</title>
      <link>https://fabifont.github.io/cheatsheets/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabifont.github.io/cheatsheets/download/</guid>
      <description>download.service (/etc/systemd/system/download.service) [Unit] Description=Download packages Wants=network-online.target After=network-online.target [Service] User=root Type=oneshot ExecStart=/bin/pacman -Syuw --noconfirm [Install] WantedBy=multi-user.target download.timer (/etc/systemd/system/download.timer) [Unit] Description=Run download.service hourly and on boot Requires=download.service [Timer] Unit=download.service OnBootSec=10s OnUnitActiveSec=1h [Install] WantedBy=timers.target Reload daemons and enable/start the timer  systemctl daemon-reload systemctl enable download.timer systemctl start download.timer  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://fabifont.github.io/cheatsheets/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabifont.github.io/cheatsheets/links/</guid>
      <description>Economy and investments  FIRE: Financial Indipendence and Early Retirement MMM: Mr. Money Mustache  Computer science  Stanford Engineering Everywhere MIT OpenCourseWare Coding Interview University Open Source Society University Awesome CS Courses Everything Computer Science Papers we love From @rcastellotti:  The Missing Semester of Your CS Education    Programming  FreeCodeCamp:  Website Youtube Github   Free Programming Books Awesome cheatsheets Codecademy  Webdev  From @rcastellotti:  A collection of free single-purpose online tools for web developers    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git</title>
      <link>https://fabifont.github.io/cheatsheets/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabifont.github.io/cheatsheets/git/</guid>
      <description>Untrack files already added to git repository based on .gitignore  commit and push all git rm -r --cached .  rm is the remove command -r will allow recursive removal –cached will only remove files from the index. Your files will still be there. The . indicates that all files will be untracked. You can untrack a specific file with git rm --cached foo.txt   git commit -m &amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packages</title>
      <link>https://fabifont.github.io/cheatsheets/packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabifont.github.io/cheatsheets/packages/</guid>
      <description>Minimal (post DE installation) code firefox gnome-keyring htop inkscape latexdraw latex-mathabx latex-pgfplots neofetch okular qemu simplescreenrecorder spectacle telegram-desktop texlive-bibtexextra texlive-fontsextra texlive-latexextra texlive-science
Full ark base bashtop bitwarden-bin bluedevil bluez-utils breeze-gtk clang cmatrix code dhcpcd discord discover dolphin dpkg drkonqi firefox geckodriver gnome-keyring gotop-bin gparted handbrake heroku-cli htop inkscape intel-ucode iwd kate kcalc kdeconnect kde-gtk-config kdenlive kdeplasma-addons kgamma5 khotkeys kinfocenter konsole kscreen ksshaskpass ktorrent kwallet-pam kwayland-integration kwrited latexdraw latex-mathabx latex-pgfplots lib32-gcc-libs liburcu libvncserver linux linux-firmware lsd lsof man-db man-pages minted mongodb-bin mongodb-compass mumble nano neofetch nerd-fonts-complete nnn okular olive openresolv oxygen pavucontrol peek pinta plasma5-applets-virtual-desktop-bar-git plasma-browser-integration plasma-desktop plasma-nm plasma-pa plasma-sdk plasma-thunderbolt plasma-vault plasma-workspace-wallpapers powerdevil pulseaudio-alsa pulseaudio-bluetooth python-pip python-pywal python-selenium python-telethon qemu reflector remmina rhino screenfetch sddm-kcm simplescreenrecorder spectacle speedtest-cli spotify teams teamviewer telegram-desktop termdown texlive-bibtexextra texlive-fontsextra texlive-kbordermatrix texlive-science tigervnc ttf-meslo ttf-roboto-mono typora ufetch-git user-manager vlc webcamoid wget whatsapp-nativefier wireguard-tools xdg-desktop-portal-kde yay zsh-autosuggestions zsh-completions zsh-syntax-highlighting zsh-theme-powerlevel10k </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 0</title>
      <link>https://fabifont.github.io/projects/project0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabifont.github.io/projects/project0/</guid>
      <description>THIS IS A TEST </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>https://fabifont.github.io/projects/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabifont.github.io/projects/project1/</guid>
      <description>THIS IS A TEST </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fabifont.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabifont.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About Hey there! I’m an italian 20 y.o guy. I have studied at ITIS Magistri Cumacini. Then I decided to get out of my comfort zone to attend Computer Science in Genoa at UniGE. I like everything tech related mostly programming.
Currently focused on C++, Java and Python.
Get my CV here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://fabifont.github.io/hobbies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fabifont.github.io/hobbies/</guid>
      <description>Hobbies I like to:
 code listen to any kind of music (except rap) watch public piano performances play games (sometimes streamed to twitch) play checkers and chess learn card tricks take care of my animals  cat (new entry) 2 dogs    These are sports I enjoy doing:
 football volleyball other sports ball related  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
